so here's an inconvenient truth all people aren't bad but all cops are i know it sucks your
grandfather who was on the force may have been a great pop pop he's a bad cop your sister who's
on the force we love sissy she's a bad cop you're uh you you who's on the force you might be like
because the system of policing is bad and the system is bigger than you and you are a part of
the system and you get your livelihood from that system and you as a part of that system will do
what that system tells you but you cannot disassociate that from who you are if that system
says we need you to go and stand at a checkpoint and harass innocent citizens you will do it and
you will say i was just doing my job if you're in england and that system tells you i would need
you to go to the park and we need you to round up all the old people who are carrying signs saying
free palestine yeah that 92 year old biddy over there never up you'll do it and you'll say i'm just
doing my job i don't know i think i just became irish but you'll do it are you stopping the system do you
think that you being in there and you know being a nice person while wearing the uniform of an oppressor
is somehow going to disassemble that system it's not it's not the truth of the matter is that you
get a pension that people don't the truth of the matter is that your co-workers who may not
by and large possess the same ethics as you are absolutely getting their cases paid by taxpayers
their job description is to protect property and to protect each other
so when we talk about policing and this whole oh but the police are here to stop crime the police do not
stop crime they respond to it the police are often criminals policing began from slave patrols
policing does not stop crime it enforces fear and if you think that fear stops crime then you don't know
anything about humans and you know what either do the cops because they only need a ged
to be on the force with a loaded weapon in yo hood you're damn rude